<resources>
    <string name="app_name">COVID VACCINATION APP</string>
    <string name="splash_text">COVID VACCINATION APP</string>
    <string name="register_splash">Register today!</string>
    <string name="dashboard">COVID</string>

    <!-- Dashboard Activity-->
    <string name="vaccines">Book slots for Covid-19 Vaccines -</string>
    <string name="call">Contact us</string>
    <string name="phone_text">Vaccine Hotline Number</string>
    <string name="title">Novel Coronavirus (2019-nCoV)</string>
    <string name="details">This app is to assist you to register for COVID-19 Vaccine and orientate you with the details necessary before proceeding with the registration process
    </string>

    <!-- Vaccine QUIZ-->
    <string name="yes_button">YES</string>
    <string name="no_button">NO</string>
    <string name="initial">0/5</string>

    <string name="correct_toast">Good!</string>
    <string name="incorrect_toast">Sorry you not qualify to register for this Vaccine!</string>

    <!-- Vaccine QUIZ Questions-->
    <string name="question_1">Are you 18 or Above\?</string>
    <string name="question_2">Are you Healthy and Certain that you are NOT having any history of severe allergies Or any medical illness\?</string>
    <string name="question_3">Do you understand that this vaccine does NOT fully guarantee you of not getting a COVID-19 infection in the future\?</string>
    <string name="question_4">Do you understand that taking this vaccine may cause reactions and side effects as described in the vaccine information\?</string>
    <string name="question_5">Are you willing to take this vaccine and ready to complete the total dose intake as scheduled\?</string>

    <!-- Register Activity-->
    <string name="vaccine_reg">Vaccine Registration</string>
    <string name="reg_success">Registration Successful</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="etEmailHint">Enter your email</string>
    <string name="tvEmailText">Email</string>
    <string name="etAddressHint">Enter your address</string>
    <string name="tvAddressText">Address</string>
    <string name="tvStateText">State</string>
    <string name="etPhoneConfirmHint">Confirm phone number</string>
    <string name="tvPhoneConfirmText">Please Confirm Your Phone Number</string>
    <string name="etPhoneHint">Enter your phone number</string>
    <string name="tvPhoneText">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="etIcPassportConfirmHint">Adhaar number</string>
    <string name="tvIcPassportConfirmText">Please Confirm Your Adhaar No </string>
    <string name="etIcPassportHint">Enter Adhaar No.</string>
    <string name="tvIcPassportText">Adhaar No</string>
    <string name="rbFemaleText">Female</string>
    <string name="rbMaleText">Male</string>
    <string name="tvGenderText">Gender</string>
    <string name="etAgeHint">Enter your age</string>
    <string name="tvAgeText">Age</string>
    <string name="etNameHint">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="tvNameText">Name</string>
    <string name="headingText">Enter Your Information</string>
    <string name="tvNameLabelText">Name:</string>
    <string name="tvAgeLabelText">Age:</string>
    <string name="tvGenderLabelText">Gender:</string>
    <string name="tvIcPassportLabelText">Adhaar No:</string>
    <string name="tvPhoneLabelText">Phone Number:</string>
    <string name="tvStateLabelText">State:</string>
    <string name="tvAddressLabelText">Address:</string>
    <string name="tvEmailLabelText">Email:</string>
    <string name="heading2Text">Registration Summary</string>
    <string name="tvVaccineNameLabelText">Vaccine Name:</string>

    <string-array name="phoneTypes">
        <item>Mobile</item>
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Work</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="states">
        <item>Select your state</item>
        <item>Andhra Pradesh</item>
        <item>Arunachal Pradesh</item>
        <item>Assam</item>
        <item>Bihar</item>
        <item>Chhattisgarh</item>
        <item>Goa</item>
        <item>Gujarat</item>
        <item>Haryana</item>
        <item>Himachal Pradesh</item>
        <item>Jharkhand</item>
        <item>Karnataka</item>
        <item>Kerala</item>
        <item>Madhya Pradesh</item>
        <item>Maharastra</item>
        <item>Manipur</item>
        <item>Meghalaya</item>
        <item>Mizoram</item>
        <item>Nagaland</item>
        <item>Odisha</item>
        <item>Punjab</item>
        <item>Rajasthan</item>
        <item>Sikkim</item>
        <item>TamilNadu</item>
        <item>Telangana</item>
        <item>Tripura</item>
        <item>UttarPradesh</item>
        <item>Uttrakhand</item>
        <item>West Bengal</item>
        <item>Andaman and Nicobar Islands</item>
        <item>Chandigarh </item>
        <item>Lakshadweep </item>
        <item>Delhi </item>
        <item>Puducherry </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="appointmentTimes">
        <item>10:00</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>14:00</item>
        <item>16:00</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="centers">LIST OF VACCINATION CENTRES</string>
    <string name="vi">VACCINE INDIA</string>
    <string name="aiims">AIIMS</string>
    <string name="balakRam">Balak Ram Hospital</string>
    <string name="nmdc">NDMC Charak Palika Hospital DH</string>
    <string name="ssv">Shri shyam vaccine</string>
    <string name="skmch">Shri Krishna Medical College</string>
    <string name="iris">IRIS Hospital</string>
    <string name="apollo">Apollo Hospitals</string>
    <string name="bansal">Bansal Hospital</string>
    <string name="max">MAX HOSPITAL</string>
    <string name="vaccineworld">VaccineWorld</string>
    <string name="spectra">Apollo Spectra</string>
    <string name="amrita">Amrita Hospital</string>
    <string name="nair">Nair Hospital</string>
    <string name="inhs">Inhs Dhanvantri</string>
    <string name="smhs">S.M.H.S. Hospital</string>

    <string name="covidshield">
        COVID SHIELD\n
                \nMINISTRY OF HEALTH INDIA
                \n01 WHAT IS COVID-19\?\n
                \nCOVID-19 disease is caused by a coronavirus called SARS-CoV-2. Symptoms may appear 2 to 14 days after exposure to the virus. Symptoms that may be experienced are:\n
                • Fever or chills\n
                • Cough\n
                • Difficulty breathing\n
                • Fatigue\n
                • Muscle or body pain\n
                • Headache\n
                • Loss of sense of taste or smell\n
                • Sore throat\n
                • Congestion or runny nose\n
                • Nausea or vomiting\n
                • Diarrhea\n
                \n
                02 WHO IS AT HIGH RISK FOR GETTING COVID-19 INFECTION\?
                \nThe risk groups are:\n
                • Children\n
                • Senior citizens aged 60 and above\n
                • Patients with chronic diseases\n
                • Patients with low immunity\n
                • Pregnant women\n
                \nCovidshield is one of the Covid-19 vaccines that has been approved for emergency\n
        \nuse in India and several other countries. It is manufactured by the Serum Institute of India (SII),\n
        \nwhich is the world\'s largest vaccine producer by volume. Covidshield is based on the viral vector\n
        \ntechnology developed by Oxford University and AstraZeneca, a British-Swedish pharmaceutical company.\n
        \nCovidshield works by introducing a modified version of a common cold virus (adenovirus) that contains \n
        \nthe genetic material of the spike protein of the novel coronavirus. The spike protein is what the coronavirus\n
        \nuses to attach to human cells and infect them. When the vaccine is injected into a person, it triggers an immune\n
        \nresponse that produces antibodies against the spike protein. These antibodies can then prevent the coronavirus from\n
        \nentering the cells and causing Covid-19.\n

\nCovidshield has been shown to be safe and effective in preventing symptomatic and severe Covid-19 across diverse populations, \n
        \nincluding older adults. According to a large phase 3 clinical trial published in the New England Journal of Medicine in December\n
        \n2021, Covidshield had an efficacy of 70.4% against symptomatic Covid-19 and 100% against severe Covid-19 and hospitalization.\n
        \nThe vaccine also demonstrated high effectiveness against various variants of the coronavirus, such as the alpha and delta variants,\n
        \nwhich are more contagious and virulent than the original strain.\n

\nCovidshield requires two doses given at an interval of 4 to 12 weeks for optimal protection. The vaccine can be stored at 2 to 8 degrees \n
        \nCelsius, which makes it suitable for distribution in low-resource settings. The vaccine is also affordable, costing around $3 per \n
        \ndose for low- and middle-income countries.\n

\nCovidshield is a vital tool in the global fight against the Covid-19 pandemic, which has claimed over 5 million lives and infected over\n
        \n250 million people worldwide. By getting vaccinated with Covidshield or any other authorized vaccine, people can protect themselves and\n
        \nothers from this deadly disease and help end the health crisis.

    </string>

    <string name="covaxin">
        COVAXIN\n
                \nMINISTRY OF HEALTH INDIA
                \n01 WHAT IS COVID-19\?\n
                \nCOVID-19 disease is caused by a coronavirus called SARS-CoV-2. Symptoms may appear 2 to 14 days after exposure to the virus. Symptoms that may be experienced are:\n
                • Fever or chills\n
                • Cough\n
                • Difficulty breathing\n
                • Fatigue\n
                • Muscle or body pain\n
                • Headache\n
                • Loss of sense of taste or smell\n
                • Sore throat\n
                • Congestion or runny nose\n
                • Nausea or vomiting\n
                • Diarrhea\n
                \n
                02 WHO IS AT HIGH RISK FOR GETTING COVID-19 INFECTION\?
                \nThe risk groups are:\n
                • Children\n
                • Senior citizens aged 60 and above\n
                • Patients with chronic diseases\n
                • Patients with low immunity\n
                • Pregnant women\n
                \n03 WHAT IS THE IMPORTANCE OF TAKING COVID 19 VACCINE\?
                \nThe COVID-19 vaccine is given to control the transmission of COVID-19 disease. As more people get vaccinated, more and more people form antibodies and in turn reduce the likelihood of more severe COVID-19 disease. Indirectly it can protect at -risk groups who are not eligible for vaccination.\n
                \nCovaxin is a COVID-19 vaccine developed by Bharat Biotech in India. \n
        It is based on an inactivated form of the coronavirus that cannot\n
        cause disease but can trigger an immune response.
        \n Covaxin has been approved for emergency use in India and several Other countries\n
        \nAccording to the results of a phase 3 clinical trial with 25,798 participants in India,\n
        \nCovaxin has an overall efficacy of 77.8% against symptomatic COVID-19. This means that it\n
        \nreduces the risk of developing symptoms\n
        \nby 77.8% compared to a placebo. The vaccine also has an efficacy of 93.4% against severe COVID-19,\n
        \nmeaning that it reduces the risk\n of hospitalization or death by 93.4%. Moreover, Covaxin has an efficacy\n
        \nof 65.2% against the Delta variant, which is the dominant strain\n
        \nin India and many other countries.\n

    </string>

    <string name="sputnikv">
        Pfizer-BioNTech\n
                \nCOVID-19 COMIRNATY VACCINE INFORMATION (PFIZER-BIONTECH COMPANY) FOR VACCINE RECIPIENTS\n
                \nWHAT IS COVID-19 \?
                \nCOVID-19 disease is caused by a coronavirus called SARS-CoV-2. Symptoms may appear 2 to 14 days after exposure to the virus. Symptoms that may be experienced are:\n
                • Fever or chills\n
                • Cough\n
                • Difficulty breathing\n
                • Fatigue\n
                • Loss of sense of taste or smell\n
                • Sore throat\n
                • Congestion or runny nose\n
                • Nausea or vomiting\n
                • Diarrhea\n
                • Muscle or body pain\n
                • Headache\n
                \n
                The risk groups are:\n
                • Children\n
                • Senior citizens aged 60 and above\n
                • Patients with chronic diseases\n
                • Patients with low immunity\n
                • Pregnant women\n
                \nWHAT IS THE IMPORTANCE OF TAKING COVID 19 VACCINE\?
                \nThe COVID-19 vaccine is given to control the transmission of COVID-19 disease. As more people get vaccinated, more and more people form antibodies and in turn reduce the likelihood of more severe COVID-19 disease. Indirectly it can protect at -risk groups who are not eligible for vaccination.\n

\nThe Sputnik V COVID-19 vaccine is one of the vaccines that have been approved for emergency use in several countries around the world. It was developed by the Gamaleya Research Institute of Epidemiology and Microbiology in Russia, and it is based on a viral vector platform.\n

\nThe vaccine uses two different adenoviruses, which are common viruses that cause colds and other mild infections, as vectors to deliver the genetic material of the coronavirus spike protein into human cells. The spike protein is what the coronavirus uses to attach to and infect cells, and by exposing the immune system to it, the vaccine aims to trigger a protective response.\n

\nThe vaccine requires two doses, administered 21 days apart, and it can be stored at 2-8°C, which makes it easier to distribute than some other vaccines that require ultra-cold storage. According to the interim results of a phase 3 trial published in The Lancet, the vaccine has an efficacy of 91.6% against symptomatic COVID-19, and it also appears to be safe and well-tolerated.\n

\n However, some experts have raised questions about the quality and transparency of the data, as well as the speed and rigor of the regulatory approval process in Russia and other countries. The vaccine has also been subject to political controversies and misinformation campaigns, which may affect public trust and acceptance.\n

\nThe World Health Organization (WHO) and the European Medicines Agency (EMA) are currently reviewing the vaccine for possible authorization. If approved, the vaccine could play an important role in increasing global vaccine supply and equity, as well as helping to end the pandemic.\n
    </string>

    <string-array name="filterStates">
        <item>Select your state</item>
        <item>Andhra Pradesh</item>
        <item>Arunachal Pradesh</item>
        <item>Assam</item>
        <item>Bihar</item>
        <item>Chhattisgarh</item>
        <item>Goa</item>
        <item>Gujarat</item>
        <item>Haryana</item>
        <item>Himachal Pradesh</item>
        <item>Jharkhand</item>
        <item>Karnataka</item>
        <item>Kerala</item>
        <item>Madhya Pradesh</item>
        <item>Maharastra</item>
        <item>Manipur</item>
        <item>Meghalaya</item>
        <item>Mizoram</item>
        <item>Nagaland</item>
        <item>Odisha</item>
        <item>Punjab</item>
        <item>Rajasthan</item>
        <item>Sikkim</item>
        <item>TamilNadu</item>
        <item>Telangana</item>
        <item>Tripura</item>
        <item>UttarPradesh</item>
        <item>Uttrakhand</item>
        <item>West Bengal</item>
        <item>Andaman and Nicobar Islands</item>
        <item>Chandigarh </item>
        <item>Lakshadweep </item>
        <item>Delhi </item>
        <item>Puducherry </item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="login_icon">Login</string>
    <string name="home_icon">Home</string>
    <string name="faq_icon">FAQ</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="login_title">Login</string>
    <string name="forgot_passwordTv">Forgot Password ?</string>
    <string name="tvPasswordText">Password</string>
    <string name="etPasswordHint">Enter password</string>
    <string name="tvPasswordConfirmText">Please Confirm Your Password</string>
    <string name="etPasswordConfirmHint">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="first_dose_appointment_date_and_time">Your First dose Appointment has been set to:</string>
    <string name="successful">Registration Successful!</string>
    <string name="unsuccessful">Sorry, Your Registration is unsuccessful, try again</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="vaccination">Vaccination</string>
    <string name="phone_number_type">Phone Number / Type</string>
    <string name="appointment_date_and_time">Appointment Date and Time</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="emailUsed">Unsuccessful Registration, this email is already used.</string>
    <string name="icUsed">Unsuccessful Registration, Adhaar number is already used.</string>
    <string name="log_out_label">Log out</string>
    <string name="txtMovingText">STAY HOME, STAY SAFE, CORONAVIRUS IS REAL, PROTECT YOURSELF AND YOUR FAMILY. REMEMBER YOUR APPOINTMENT DATE AND ENCOURAGE YOUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY TO TAKE THE VACCINE...DO NOT HESITATE TO CONTACT THE NEAREST HOSPITAL IF YOU NOTICE ANY CORONAVIRUS SYMPTOMS </string>
    <string name="searchLabelTitle">Search</string>

    <string name="faqQuestion1">What is corona virus \?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer1">Coronaviruses are a group of related RNA viruses that cause diseases in mammals and birds. In humans and birds, they cause respiratory tract infections that can range from mild to lethal. The most recent coronavirus disease is COVID-19. It is an infectious disease caused by the SARS-CoV-2 virus. Most people infected with the virus will experience mild to moderate respiratory illness and recover without requiring special treatment. However, some will become seriously ill and require medical attention.</string>

    <string name="faqQuestion2">How do I make an appointment\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer2">Your appointment will be made once you have completed the questionnaire by visiting the Dashboard and click on any vaccine you want to register. Your answers  to the quiz will determine whether you will be able to proceed with the vaccine registration and an appointment will be scheduled after successful registration. You can then Login to check if any changes occur.
    </string>

    <string name="faqQuestion3">What should I do if my current location is not available\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer3">Login, and click on List of vaccine administration and you can see the nearest location near you</string>

    <string name="faqQuestion4">Are there any hotline numbers I can call to find out more about the COVID-19 vaccination registration\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer4">Go to Dashboard and click on the Vaccine hotline Number and you can dial it directly on this app once you click it</string>

    <string name="faqQuestion5">I have registered for vaccination. What Next\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer5">Vaccination candidates will receive confirmation of date and assigned Vaccination Distribution Centre PPV two weeks before their scheduled appointment. Within the two weeks, candidates will also get reminders via phone call or SMS.</string>

    <string name="faqQuestion6">When will I know all appointment details\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer6">Vaccination candidates will receive confirmation of date and assigned Vaccination Distribution Centre PPV two weeks before their scheduled appointment. Within the two weeks, candidates will also get reminders via phone call or SMS.</string>

    <string name="faqQuestion7">What is comorbidity and how will I know if I have it\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer7">Comorbidity is when an individual has preExisting health conditions like high blood pressure, diabetes, heart disease, kidney disease, liver disease, low immunity, asthma, cancer, chronic lung disease, stroke or obesity. Comorbidity can only be certified by qualified medical professionals.
    </string>

    <string name="faqQuestion8">I have high blood pressure and high cholesterol but it is under control and I need no medication. Does that mean I have comorbidity\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer8">Please consult a qualified medical professional to determine your current comorbidity status.</string>

    <string name="faqQuestion9">I recently underwent a surgery to remove a growth. Does that mean I have comorbidity\?</string>
    <string name="faqAnswer9">Yes. Although the growth has been removed, you are still considered to have comorbidity.</string>
    <string name="vaccine_centersBtnLabel">View Vaccine Administration Centers</string>
    <string name="tvFilterText">Filter State By :</string>
    <string name="tvAppointTteLabel">Time:</string>
    <string name="tvAppointDteLabel">Date:</string>
    <string name="welcomeText">Login</string>
    <string name="textInputLayoutEmailText">Email</string>
    <string name="textInputLayoutPasswordText">Password</string>
    <string name="btn_loginText">Login</string>
    <string name="btn_registerText">Register</string>
    <string name="not_registered_yet">Not Registered Yet?</string>
    <string name="tvQuestionFAQText">Question Name</string>
    <string name="tvAnswerFAQText">Answer TexView</string>
    <string name="location_nameText">Vaccines</string>
    <string name="covid_19_vaccination">Covid-19 Vaccination</string>
    <string name="register_today">Register Today</string>
    <string name="tvEditText">Edit User</string>
    <string name="tvAppDateText">Date of Vaccine Appointment</string>
    <string name="btnDateText">Pick A Date</string>
    <string name="tvAppTimeText">Time of Vaccine Appointment</string>
    <string name="btAddText">Update User</string>


</resources>